Kellie Cuitino 7692 Fairgrove Ave. Windermere, FL 34786 630-639-6937

Experienced merchandiser with a demonstrated history of working in the entertainment industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Fundraising, Clerical Skills, Microsoft Excel, and Multi-line Phone. Strong sales professional with a Certificate focused in General Office Occupations and Clerical Services from College of DuPage.

Experience

WALT DISNEY WORLD

Dream Maker

May 2017 – Present

Stock and pull items for basket makers and in-room celebrations. Deliver baskets to resorts and set up in room celebrations for guests

Vacation Planner

Jan 2017 - Present

Sell tickets to guest visiting WDW. Help plan their day. Help navigate app

Reservations Agent

Sep 2016 – Jan 2017

Answer calls from guests booking vacations at WDW. Get guest information provide quotes and take payments

DELNOR HOSPITAL

Registrar

Jun 2013 - Aug 2016

Communicates with patients and guests including greeting them upon arrival, confirming identity and providing necessary information related to their visit. Completes check-in/out functions as directed. Confirms and updates patient identification and demographic/insurance information. Completes patient registration as needed. Obtains patient consents

Kellie Cuitino 7692 Fairgrove Ave. Windermere, FL 34786 630-639-6937

Hostess

Sep 2012 – Jun 2013

This position is responsible for passing meal trays to patients, entering patient food intake information, ensuring pantry fridges maintain correct temperatures and stocking pantries.

NYULI CHIROPRACTIC

OFFICE ASSISTANT

September 2011 - September 2013

Responsible for keeping all patient files organized and to maintain the front office. File medical records and handle administrative duties, such as answering phones and **scheduling appointments**. These administrative and also responsible for **managing** insurance forms.

MOSAIC SALE SOLUTIONS

Merchandising Specialist

May 2008 - September 2011

Maximize visual presentation by stocking, facing, and pricing products Create product awareness and added value placement opportunities in-store

Perform POG resets and audits

Scan and report stock levels by title to generate order information.

UNITED HEALTHCARE

Supervise Small Business Quotation Department

1993-1996

Develop and maintain high level of communication with customer regarding status of RFQ Establish Cost and List Price matrices to deliver consistent and timely customer quotations Determine RFQ priorities and policies Develop firm relationships to increase communication and productivity Evaluate employees and training.

Education

UCF Boot Coding Bootcamp - Currently Attending

College of Dupe

Kellie Cuitino 7692 Fairgrove Ave. Windermere, FL 34786 630-639-6937

References

Upon request